THE GIRL FROM TRIESTE
What's up with her?
She's drowning!
Push it, come on!
Hurry!
Look at that!
Doesn't know how to swim
and still goes out.
Nothing surprises me anymore.
But she's going to make it.
Tony, give her
something to drink.
- Can you stand by yourself?
- Yes, thank you.
You know
you barely made it?
That's true.
- Drink, it will do you good.
- Tony, give us also one.
One after another.
Where are your clothes?
The sea must have washed them away.
Give me another.
Thank you.
- Give me a drink as well.
- Of course.
I'll leave,
please give me the lobster.
Here you go. Have a good day.
You're leaving already?
- You were scared, eh?
- Not at all.
It was very beautiful.
Beautiful?
Yes. Especially
when they rescued me.
It was extraordinary.
I felt loved.
I felt something.
Ciao, Tony.
Goodbye, Mr. Dino.
If you do not bring me back my plaid
I will notify the police.
Hello!
They told me you lived here.
Is this your house?
Nice.
Yes, I like it too.
These are my drawings!
You threw them away, remember.
They are mine now.
No one wants to take them from you.
Tell me one thing.
What do you really want from me?
Can I come in with you for a moment?
Sure.
Sorry, could you hold this for me?
- That okay?
- Sure.
- It's beautiful here.
- I'm not complaining.
My name is Nicole.
So you're French?
My mother is French.
Dad met her in Paris.
He was a diplomat.
Nicole and further?
I know your name.
Dino, Dino Romani.
Exactly.
You make comics?
Like Charlie Brown?
Charlie Brown is a character.
The designer is named Schulz.
You're as famous as him?
But your drawings are beautiful.
It's true.
That's enough for me.
So?
What do you want to do?
Give you back your plaid of course.
Nothing else?
Don't you want to make love?
I love to make love.
Stay beside me.
I like being caressed afterwards.
You're thirsty?
I will be right back.
Hey
Who is she?
Beauty.
Beauty, Nicole.
Very pleased.
But Beauty, thou hast no face?
It is being born.
A gorgeous body.
She has no taboo.
I want her to be a kind of
symbol of innocence.
Provocative, without knowing it.
Like me?
I said without knowing it.
You believe you can see through me, right?
It's not difficult.
You know
Today at the beach
I only pretended I was drowning.
I can swim very well.
And you act very well.
- You mock me?
- No.
Is this the new game among your friends?
No.
I'm doing tests.
Tests?
I make myself drown
like today.
Or I lie on the road,
as if I had been hit by a car.
Or I simulate suicide with
some sedatives, for example.
And if someone comes and tries to
save me, then
I feel loved
and regain my identity.
Your identity?
Proof that the world
knows I exist.
Why do you look at me that way?
I wish she had your face.
Who? Beauty?
You should pose for me.
I'll be happy with half an hour.
Why not.
I have nothing to wear.
I have a wardrobe full of
women's clothes. Choose one.
From your wife?
I am not married.
Tony already told me.
But I wanted to hear what you would tell me.
It's best to close the door, no?
I did not want to offend you,
forgive me.
But what is it, now?
Sorry.
Why did you want
to close the door?
I want a man who loves me
also when I pee.
Whose clothes are all these?
Who cares.
Tony told me you lived alone.
- And you go soon.
- Tony talks too much.
Is it true you go?
Within a few weeks.
You do not like people, huh?
A small dose.
The fewer there are, the better.
Me, it's the opposite.
I hate loneliness.
Each his thing.
Exactly.
And you, where you live?
In an old villa
near San Justo.
There is a garden
with Greek columns.
And a big beautiful tree in front.
And an army of servants.
A cook
Butler and four good.
Well, you have to be wealthy.
I have everything I want.
And even more!
Well, I'll prepare food.
It starts when you're ready.
Are you ready?
Good morning.
You remember the girl
who was rescued the other day?
- Have you seen her?
- I know who that is.
Surely one of these a looser,
one day here, the other way ...
It's not serious. Thank you, anyway.
It is immediately to the right
the end of the square.
- Thank you.
- I beg you.
I have not found. Where are you?
Nicole.
I did not expect, my darling!
- I should know.
- Nothing.
But I have an appointment tonight.
Come with me, it is among
The Stanui, you remember?
Annoying but harmless.
No, it tells me nothing.
I just wanted to sleep.
You're home, you know the.
But eat something,
promised?
Promised.
Hello, my pretty.
Have fun.
I'll be back before midnight.
Hello?
You have nothing to say?
What is your real name?
I found a bracelet
with the initial''C''R d.
R is for what?
Rosa? Rita? Renata?
So you do not want to talk?
Can I come?
- Why?
- I bring you the dress.
- Where is she?
- What?
The dress.
I've forgotten.
You forgot something else.
D C''R''.
What makes you laugh?
R d''C''is the name of the merchant.
I do not call Renata
- But Nicole.
- So it was you over the phone?
- You have taken the time?
- While you were sleeping.
They are beautiful.
It is you who are beautiful.
On it, I had
make a horrible nightmare.
I do not love Him.
I look dead.
- You slept.
- Dead I am like that.
Tear-La.
The tear, I beg you.
The tear, I say!
You're a funny girl, Nicole.
You also have a surname?
That could be.
But I forgot the.
I bet you do not believe me.
Exactly, I do not believe you.
It's true.
There is so much
I do not remember.
When you do not love,
we try to forget.
You do not love?
I think you're beautiful!
Because if I want,
I can seduce.
I dressed in real lady.
Tonight I want to go out with you.
I can not say no
a real lady.
I want you to share a detail.
What?
The villa which you spoke
would need work.
- Thank you.
- I beg you.
I do not mind ...
It amused me
you do not tell me anything about you,
but lie to me more.
This was not a lie,
but a fantasy.
You do not like it?
Like that your father?
- The diplomat?
- I never knew my father.
This place bores me.
It is stifling here.
It amuses you?
Why? I do not do anything wrong.
No. You're fantastic, I know the.
- Shall we?
- If this is your desire.
Justino?
Sir?
Madam ... no longer hungry.
Another time.
Of course, sir. Thank you.
Madam, your shoes.
- Good evening.
- Bye.
You saw how I am hard.
You're right, I still tremble.
You had your shot prepared, eh?
I do not anticipate that I will
one minute to the other.
Needless to search.
If they stop,
you do not have your papers?
I have never on me.
- A relative of yours?
- Who?
Giuliano Tomita.
What is wrong with you?
- Looks like you're the police!
- Come, calm yourself.
Give me a cigarette.
It's your brother?
I have neither brother nor sister,
if you want to know.
- Your husband?
- I am not married.
- But I'll be in the month.
- Congratulations.
Now you know
why I behave this way.
Who is then?
His name is Michele.
I met him at university.
- At the university?
- Right.
I study English literature,
I am preparing my thesis.
I also have a job,
for your information, archivist.
And then there was Francesca
studying architecture.
Who?
- Francesca.
- Who is it?
It is the former girlfriend Michele.
She loves him still.
- We saw all three together.
- If you're going ...
You do not believe a word
what I said?
- Should I?
- Why not?
But still ...
if you're in love with Michele,
What are you doing with me?
I did not say
I was in love with him.
I said that I married.
It's true.
- He knows you love him?
- Sure.
Why not marry
Francesca? She, she loves him.
- Because he loves me.
- But you do not love her.
It's you that I love!
You're funny when you sleep.
I wanted to know your reaction
seeing that I had disappeared.
I wondered
if you seek me.
I love you. Nicole.
If you come,
wait for me, if you like.
The door is open.
Tomita? It's here.
- Where?
- On the first floor.
- I take the stairs?
- Yes. The last door on the right.
Please?
- Looking for Miss Tomita.
- You found it.
Nicole Tomita.
No, Francesca Tomita.
Who is Giuliano Tomita?
It's my father.
It becomes complicated.
You need to get my friend,
Nicole Roselli.
This is a big liar!
You do not live with it
and a Michele?
- It was there two years.
- Where does she?
I've lent him my car
there three months, I do not have the magazine.
Nicole is like that.
Yes, I've noticed.
She said
she married Michele.
Michele?
But I'm the wife.
You're going to marry?
It took you by boat, right?
It was me all the air.
This is ridiculous.
You know where it can be?
I know the name
one of her friends.
I'll try that.
It's unbelievable, no?
We are good friends,
yet I know very little about it.
But you know Nicole,
it is mysterious.
She goes, she comes
Here she is, she is gone.
You can not help me?
A phone, an address?
- A name?
- I can not help you.
Imagine
I do not even remember
The when I met her!
Well ...
I've pretty bored.
You did not at all disturbed.
If you ever see The ...
- I tell him that you are looking for the.
- Thank you.
Surprised?
You have not forgotten?
Val ... I have not seen your car.
It is behind I am discreet.
Her name is Nicole?
She is very pretty.
You take on the cradle
now?
As if you did not know!
It does not bother
I still use your home?
How are you, Valeria?
I'm doing.
You have too much heart.
You deserve to meet
a man who can appreciate you.
I think to seek him, thank you.
I forgot ...
I lent one of your dresses to Nicole.
- She was naked?
- It would have been amazing!
I'm jaded
but with her
I go from one surprise.
Did she hang?
The roles are reversed,
it will do you good!
I've never been able to hide.
Right?
What is it advanced me?
All is not over between us?
It is you who are mysterious.
I found
a friend who is very dear.
Excuse me.
Where are the keys to your car?
On contact.
I was alone again.
Me ran away,
I had a drink in a square
I stayed there,
bare legs, raised,
Until they noticed me.
I felt better, less alone.
They will remember me,
exist.
These pigs looking at me
I could feel their desire ...
They needed me,
m they loved him somehow.
So you are There?
Where have you been
all day?
Professor Marin you looking for.
You can still see Him,
He is in his office.
Enter!
So?
We have often talked about.
Listen.
This is not attracting
the attention that you will solve
- Your problems, your loneliness.
- What is the solution?
In any case, not go to a place
show off ...
- Do not show off ...
- Exhibiting my cat?
The reason you do not say?
You're a doctor, you did not
to be afraid of words.
Not Words
that scare me,
but the use made of it.
Why do not you go back
see the man whom you spoke?
I changed my mind.
Why?
He is a liar!
You're wrong.
You did not say ...
I tell him anything.
I never know it.
You should stop
out some time.
Say one week.
You want to punish myself?
I just ask
a small sacrifice.
Thou must help me.
I need to take care of you.
You want to heal, is not it?
More than anything.
You do not have the magazine?
No sign of her.
I do not believe you.
Tell me why
you give yourself this May?
How?
Why are you looking for Nicole?
It's worth the trouble?
You know where she is.
You're wrong!
Why not tell me the truth?
Let me hide you?
Nicole is a whore?
A call girl?
Please, Mr. Romani.
You become insulting.
And you, what are you? Madam?
Where is Nicole?
It is better that you leave,
you're drunk.
It's the least of my worries.
Good evening.
So I lied.
I told
that I married Michele.
I'm really mad.
But I really like it.
This is the first time
I feel this feeling.
For him I want to heal.
I do not want to hurt him.
We made a pact.
I would go out just a few hours.
I can not stay like that
I've got the track
I explain, at least.
Then you let yourself heal?
I promise.
The You know, I want to heal.
And you will be cured.
You think someone
who knows nothing about me
may suspect
I have the sick mind?
It is beautiful, your spirit.
Wait, dammit!
Where were you like that?
I could not find your house.
You're Here!
You came.
I've just missed?
I did that get you.
Where?
I went everywhere, Miss Roselli.
- Who told you my name?
- Some Francesca
who will marry a certain Michele.
You've met?
No.
What did she say?
Not much.
No more than your friend Clara.
Many words
zero information.
Get dressed.
Why?
Dress yourself and you'll know the.
Where are we going?
You wanted to know where I live?
The show I'm going.
Between.
This is where I live.
This is my house.
If you want to find ...
I know where to find you.
End of mystery.
You live here alone?
The maid is sick.
So, you live alone?
My mother is in London.
I leave the morrow.
I'll stay a month.
A month?
This will be the last time.
Then
it will separate again.
I return in a month.
I promise.
Completed Running away.
I want to live
with you forever.
Because I love you.
If you like me ...
Of course I want from you.
What do we do, my love?
We go to a restaurant?
Or in bed?
I have too many things to do.
All right.
Tomorrow, I'll take you to the airport.
I hate the goodbyes.
Do not complicate it.
Go now.
Do as
if we see tomorrow.
I do not pretend,
but I'll try.
Good.
I'll write you all the days.
I swear.
I'll miss you, Nicole.
Many.
London, May 27
My love, I'm just arrived
i miss you already.
From my window I see the park.
It's a beautiful day.
But you're not there
and I am sad.
Send one every day.
I have the numbered
adhesive stamps on top.
Okay, I will.
Talk about a break!
- You are married in London?
- Not here.
- We got married yesterday.
- Really?
- I wish them happiness.
- Thank you.
- I hope all goes well.
- Me too.
''I do not exist!''
''I want
be one of your drawings!''
Give! It's me who have found it!
I want to read it.
''My life will change.''
The first is''
I'm in love.''
The Give Me!
''I want
be one of his drawings!''
The Give Me!
The You want?
Farm Gate!
What do you want?
You're going to see
you do what you want!
- What is it?
- Kind of a bitch!
You expose your pussy
Place on Unita?
''I'm in love!''
''I want to be a picture!''
Leave me!
Help!
You will see, damn!
Bitch!
I realized that I could
live without you.
When you're not there
I have pleasure in anything.
I lose the reason
if I do not know
that you exist and that you don 't wait.
Because you don 't wait,
is not it?
Keep the good.
Come, my dear, courage.
Glucose.
We'll get him out of the coma.
I would like these days
are shorter.
Don 't want it,
I do not give you my address.
That is not
tempt you to join me.
This division
is tested.
I want you to be sure
want to live with me.
As I'm sure she wants
spend my life with you.
Do you love me?
Me, I love you. Nicole.
Do not worry, Clara.
His condition is improving, believe me.
But if I see the ...
- It is too early.
- You will tell me?
Sure.
Nicole Kiss for me.
Some people
can not face reality.
All injured.
Nicole is the former.
A heightened sensitivity.
- What is it?
- What difference does it make?
If I told you that it is
manic-depressive
or schizophrenic
or simply neurotic
that's not the important thing.
She is in coma
under control.
On The fate of the coma
then it plunges into new,
was awakened again,
and is it dived
so, 30 or 40 times.
We call
this treatment coma insulin.
It acts on the psyche of the patient.
It is unclear why it stabilizes them,
but it has beneficial effects.
We hope to go to Nicole
- Balance.
- This will be long?
Hard to say.
She had made great progress,
She seemed almost healed.
We almost
The decided to leave out, then ...
there about a month
Something happened there.
You've said enough about me, thank you.
- Hello?
- Hello. Dr. Marino.
Nicole is with you?
So it does not go away.
It was released this morning
without my permission.
Yes, I am sure
she will go home.
No, I do have him say anything.
She does not know that you know.
Do not ask me
what to do.
It's your problem.
This choice is yours.
Dino?
Go away.
Where we going?
In Afghanistan, China.
Where you want.
Venice, alright with you?
Here or elsewhere ...
If you do not care,
we could have stayed home.
You do not understand
I wanted to escape?
Excuse me, but I'm thinking.
That's how you see
trip? You with your whiskey
and I who make the conversation?
It would be too selfish
- Although it is tempting me!
- Please!
One year ...
What?
Brazil.
- It's been a year.
- It was a delight.
We ate too much papaya.
- We spend the afternoon here?
- You want to move?
Good idea!
So, let's go.
You're in my hands now.
I know.
I love you still.
I'm sorry.
Let, I'll drive.
Val?
Where are we?
End the trip.
You want a coffee?
No, thank you.
You hate me?
I hate lots of things,
but not you.
What can I do
to thank you?
I'll send the note.
Good luck.
London, 1 June 3
Dino, I do not know
if I succeed to explain,
but I'll try.
I met a man, Roberto.
We fell in love.
It's been love at first sight,
as during a summer storm.
We got married yesterday.
Roberto Canadian
we leave tomorrow in Montreal.
Do not try to find me.
Remember me
and please,
do not hate me. Goodbye. Nicole.
Since when you know The?
When?
When you came home,
I hid myself.
I know. I had understood.
Poor Dino ...
Then I wanted to flee you,
I'm gone.
With that in which clothes,
I was surprised that with you,
The other day.
This dirty whore.
I love you, Nicole.
This is unfortunate,
because I do not love you anymore.
Yes, I remember.
You like Roberto now
one you married.
I lied.
Why?
Because I am a liar!
I do not know how to tell
I do not love you anymore.
You love me!
It's not true!
Listen.
Come live with me.
Do not tell me that,
while jostling in my head.
- Go away, please.
- Not without you.
The Thou must understand.
You can not leave me alone!
You're as crazy as me.
The I think.
But you've never seen
when I scream,
when I do not recognize anyone anymore
when I hallucinate.
The I bear.
Sometime. Sometimes
I do not even know who I am!
What took you
to love a girl like me?
If you want to know if it works,
we must try.
You do not know what you say.
You can help me?
Not sure.
Life is dangerous.
Like Love.
What time is it?
8am, 9am, who knows?
- From the morning or evening?
- I will see.
Evening.
You hungry?
You want to eat here?
No need to get excited,
we have already said enough.
I know you're in New York
and I'm in Paris ...
Do not worry,
I see Charlie tonight.
I tell him. Hello.
Who was that?
It is not worth the trouble to speak.
She was a woman, eh?
What woman?
It was for my work.
I understand, will.
You do not understand.
There is only one woman
in my life.
And it's you.
Is that clear?
No, please.
Come in.
Put it There.
I must
as if I had not seen?
When you leave Paris?
As soon as I bore myself.
You have a beautiful dress.
That's why I fly!
There is so that you hide!
- Hi!
- Hi, Charlie.
So? You know Danielle?
- Yes. How are you?
- Well, do you?
It is time to go.
I'll join you in a moment.
- Are you staying long?
- I'm leaving in three days.
London and New York.
Want
I convey a message?
Tell them to calm down,
I will deliver on time.
- The book comes out at Christmas.
- The Harry told me.
Looking for who? A girl?
Yes, my friend. It has disappeared.
Claude had to take him up there
watch the documentary.
He has reported from the Middle East.
It's fantastic.
You know Claude!
Yes, I know the. See you later.
Have fun.
There! Now!
Come, let us go.
Let's go.
That's better.
Still with me,
and I will not be afraid.
I will not be afraid of anything.
I wish there
more than you and me.
Just two of us.
I want to go to the house.
I will stand by you, my darling.
We go to the house.
It's good to see you!
I can take you home.
- Are you happy?
- Yes, very. Happiness is.
- There will be enough space?
- Yes, I think.
- Where I put my clothes?
- Wherever you want.
You're at home here.
I think I'll be happy.
Sure you'll be the.
Only me.
- Your new tenant.
- Leave on.
- Are you going out?
- Yes, I go to the beach.
- You put me in color?
- Flaming.
For my Beauty
spring from the board!
I am full of energy.
The coffee is on the stove,
you just turn it on
and wait until the water boils.
While you wait,
The kitchen puts a bit.
Yes, sir.
Go away.
Go away!
- Come quickly! They scare me!
- What is it?
Send them away, I beg you!
- Help me!
- But what? There is nothing.
Cockroaches!
- Everywhere!
- There is none.
- Believe me.
- Make the go.
- I beg you.
- Everything is fine.
Where they are,
now?
It's everywhere.
On the floor.
Yes, I am the hunt.
My God!
I have in the hair!
They are Here.
Caimi, my love.
There are more.
I'm still in the hair.
The I still feel.
But no.
There is none.
There never has been.
But I have the felt.
- For real.
- I know ...
It's over now.
You have beautiful hair.
If long.
I hope that this is
as a temporary crisis.
She takes medication
regularly?
Yes, I think.
Well ...
And for your wedding
- You set the date?
- Not yet.
Soon.
It's a good idea.
This marriage could help.
That could make him
stability.
I hope so.
It's worth a try, right?
Yes, it is very important.
You said to Nicole
you come see me?
She was sleeping when I left.
It was cairn.
It is better
that you're waking up.
Call me if needed.
- At any time.
- Thanks, of course.
Enough Enough
I'm exhausted!
Enough
What's up?
Caimi now!
Stop the bell!
- I'm Doing.
- The Stop!
I beg you, do the quiet.
I beg you!
Make the stop!
I'll go away.
I just know
she was going home.
There is about three hours.
No, she was well.
Wait, I think it is Here.
Okay, I'll tell him.
It was Clara.
I have not gone home.
- You want to know where I was?
- Yes.
Good God ...
- It's you that I have said.
- Me?
You said
- They were too Long.
- No.
I said they were
Long and beautiful.
I disgust you?
- Tell Him.
- Not at all.
It is the element of surprise,
let me get used to it.
Answer honestly.
I please you
like that?
You always like.
It's true.
I think you're very sexy.
Really?
I swear.
So prove to me.
Let's get to bed.
Do not tempt me,
I should finish Beauty.
I'll join you later, OK?
Here Earth, to you.
It's you who have taken?
The Tell me.
What?
Letter.
What Letter?
Newsletter Roberto.
The one he sent me to London.
Roberto does not exist.
It's you who have invented
remember.
Do not touch me.
London, September 25.
Nicole, I can not
live without you.
I come for you.
When we are together,
there will be neither winter, nor rain,
nor snow, nor cold.
Nothing but the sun.
Good morning.
You've worked all night?
More or less.
It is you who put me in bed?
You were asleep on the couch.
How do you feeling?
Perfectly.
There was the sun,
it's a beautiful day.
I prayed so that there
the sun today. He is Here
just for me.
I'll go
enjoy on the beach.
I'll come.
Do not come.
You're tired.
I must rest.
It does not matter
I want to go with you.
I'm out.
Do what you want ...
Thank you, Tony.
Who would have thought it?
There was four months, on The recovered,
and now ...
There was barely four months.
When you asked me
if I knew the ...
I wanted to tell you something,
but I dared not.
What?
In your place,
I paid attention.
- Must live dangerously.
- It's true!
www.rarelust.com